Guide to the Science Fiction and Comic Fanzine Collection, 1952-2005 SC.1980.02
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Science Fiction and Comic Fanzine Collection
1952-2005
1967-1980
ULS Archives & Special Collections
University of Pittsburgh
SC.1980.02
14 Linear Feet (11 boxes)
The collection contains science fiction and comic fanzines, published both locally and nationally, between 1956 and 2005. A bulk of the collection is from the 1970's.
History
A fanzine defined, is "a non-professional and non-official publication produced by enthusiasts of a particular cultural phenomenon for the pleasure of others who share their interest." Fanzines were actually popularized within science fiction fandom before being adopted by other communities. Before the internet, fanzines provided people a vehicle to share thoughts, ideas, activities, art, and critique. The zines were often times produced at home, libraries, schools, and anywhere that allowed access to mimeograph machines and later, photocopiers. Science fiction and comic fanzines are a great resource for those interested in tracing the history of fandom and the subculture as a whole.
Scope and Content Notes
The Science Fiction and Comic Fanzine collection includes fanzines published primarily in the United States, including a considerable amount published locally and regionally and some of foreign origin. Contents of the fanzines include reviews, opinion, short fiction, letters, cartoons and drawings, and an exchange of information about science fiction conventions and fan interests.
Arrangement
The collection is divided into the following three series, arranged alphabetically:
Series I. Comic Fanzines
Series II. Science Fiction Fanzines
Series III. Related Materials
Previous Citation
Science Fiction and Fanzine Collection, 1952-2005, SC.1980.02, Special Collections Department, University of Pittsburgh
Acquisition Information
The fanzine collection originated from multiple donors, including members of the Pittsburgh Comix Club and individual science fiction and comic fans from Pittsburgh.
Science fiction -- Societies, etc.; Science fiction, American; Fantasy; Fan magazines; Self-publishing; Comic book; Marvel comics; University of Pittsburgh
- Comic Fanzines, 1952-2005; I.
  Scope and Content Notes
  This series includes comic fanzines created between 1958 and 1983 that reflect a vareity of comic book fandom and include general interest as well as fanzines devoted to specific titles and characters. While the series contains predominately fanzines, also included are some amateur and underground comic books and collector guides.
  The series is organized alphabetically and when possible, the publication information, including location, publisher and editors(s) are noted in the scope and content notes.
  - Adventure Scene, 1975; 1 issue (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Edited by Carl J. Horak.
  - The Adventuress, 1975-1977; 4 issues (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Published in Baltimore, MD and edited by Al Tanner.
  - AFTA: Ascension From The Ashes, 1978; 1 issue (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Published at Rutgers University in New Brunswick, NJ and edited by Bill-Dale Marcinko.
  - Afterwords: The Art and Story Newsletter, 1977; 1 issue (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Published in Fresno, CA and edited by James D. Denney.
  - All Dynamic, 1970; 1 issue (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Published in East Moine, IL and edited by Alan L. Light.
  - All-Time All-TIme, 1973; 1 issue (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Published in Berwyn, IL and edited by Gary Ricker.
  - Alter Ego, 1964-1969; 3 issues (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Published in St. Louis, MO and edited by Roy Thomas.
  - Andromeda, 1974; 1 issue (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Published in London, Ontario, Canada and edited by Bill Paul.
  - Art and Story, 1976; 2 issues (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Published in Bogota, NJ and edited by James D. Denney.
  - Auction Block, 1969; 1 issue (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Published in La Belle/Oak Park, MI and edited by Tom Altschuler and Rick Dey.
  - Badtime Stories, 1971; 1 issue (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Published by Graphic Masters Publishers in Great Neck, NY and edited by Ron Barlow.
  - The Barsoomian, 1952-1954; 3 issues (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Published in Rochester, NY and edited by Joseph W. Miller.
  - Barsoomian Bazaar, 1968- 1971; 3 issues (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Published in Kansas City, MO by the House of Greystoke.
  - Batmania, 1964-1976; 17 issues (Box 1, Folder 14-15)
    Published in Columbia, MO by the White House of Comics and edited by Biljo White.
  - Beastiality, 1976; 1 issue (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Publishd by Apandamandis Productions and edited by Greg Spagnola.
  - Beyond Infinity, 1 issue (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Published in Vannuys, CA and edited by R. Gustaveson.
  - Big Barda Believers, 1972; 1 issue (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Published in Auburndale, MA and edited by Mark Antranig.
  - Blackjack, 1 issue (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Published in Eerie, PA and edited by Larry Walczak.
  - Bronze Shadows, 1966-1968; 8 issues (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Published in Grand Haven, MI and edited by Fred S. Cook.
  - Bull Dog, 1973-1976; 7 issues (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Published in Lynnwood, WA and edited by Steve Kristiansen.
  - Bull Dog Barks, 1974; 1 issue (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Edited by Steve Kristiansen.
  - The Burroughs Bibliophiles, 1 issue (Box 1, Folder 23)
    A directory of Edgar Rice Burroughs fans, appears to be related to The Burroughs Bulletin.
  - The Burroughs Bulletin, 1969-1976; 10 issues (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Published by Edgar Rice Burroughs, Inc. and House of Greystoke in Kansas City, MO and edited by Vernell Coriell.
  - Captain America Story, 1 issue (Box 1, Folder 25)
    Published by The Little Wise Guys From Daredevil Comics. Appears to be an inner page from a longer fanzine.
  - Cartonaggio: A Journal of Bildegraphics, 1978-1980; 6 issues (Box 1, Folder 26)
    Edited by Dr. Alfred D. (Fred) Stewart.
  - The Cartoon Museum, 1971; 1 issue (Box 1, Folder 27)
    Published in Orlando, FL and edited by Jim Ivey.
  - Cartoonews, 1975-1977; 2 issues (Box 1, Folder 28)
    Published in Orlando, FL and edited by Jim Ivey and Bill Sheridan.
  - Cartoonist Profiles, 1978; 2 issues (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Published in New York, NY by Winchester Press and edited by Jud Hurd.
  - CCM Newsletter, 1979-1980; 6 issues (Box 1, Folder 30)
    Published in Maplewood, NJ by Interlude Productions and edited by David Caruba.
  - Cerebro, 1980; 1 issue (Box 1, Folder 31)
    Published in Somerset, UK and edited by Geoff Lamprey.
  - Champion, 1966; 2 issues (Box 1, Folder 32)
    Published in Braintree, MA by Champion Publications and edited by Bob Cosgrove.
  - Changes, 1 issue (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Interior pages only.
  - Chapters, 1980; 3 issues (Box 1, Folder 34)
    Published in Cambridge, MA by Devil's Trident and edited by Leo Giroux, Jr., Laura W. Giroux, Richard Howell and Carol Kalish.
  - Chronicle, 1974-1975; 2 issues (Box 1, Folder 35)
    Published in Chicago, IL by Windy City Enterprises and edited by George S. Breo.
  - Chronicles, 1975; 1 issue (Box 1, Folder 36)
    Edited by Steve Clement, Nick Fiasco, H. Dean Cupec and Dave Mosser.
  - City Limits Gazette, 1981-1983; 10 issues (Box 1, Folder 37)
    Published in Seattle, WA and edited by Bruce Chrislin.
  - The Collector, 1967-1974; 27 issues (Box 1, Folder 38-39)
    Published in Clairton, PA and edited by Bill G. Wilson.
  - The Collector Spectacular Special, 1969; 1 issue (Box 1, Folder 40)
    Pubished in Clairton, PA by Prince Printing and edited by Bill G. Wilson.
  - Collector's Dream, 1978; 2 issues (Box 1, Folder 41)
    Published in Buffalo, NY by G&T (George & Tony) Enterprises.
  - Collector's Guide: The First Heroic Age, 1969; 1 issue (Box 1, Folder 42)
    Published in Detroit, MI by Panelologist Publications and edited by Jerry G. Bails.
  - Comic Art News and Reviews, 1973; 1 issue (Box 1, Folder 43)
    Published in Kitchener, Ontario, Canada and edited by John Balge.
  - Comic Book, 1966; 1 issue (Box 1, Folder 44)
    Published in Chicago, IL and edited by Alan J. Hanley.
  - Comic Comments, 1966; 1 issue (Box 1, Folder 45)
    Published in Tampa, FL by Sunshine Publications and edited by Gary Brown.
  - Comic Crusader, 1968-1976; 11 issues (Box 1, Folder 46-47)
    Edited by Martin L. Greim.
  - Comic and the Crypt, 1971-1972; 3 issues (Box 1, Folder 48)
    Published in Toronto, Ontario, Canada by Comic and Crypt Publications and edited by Mark Sigal and David Rubin.
  - Comic Detective, 1972-1973; 2 issues (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Published in Ponca City, OK by Comic Detective Research Society and edited by Bart Bush.
  - Comic Fandom Monthly, 1971; 7 issues (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Published in Brooklyn, NY and edited by Joe Brancatelli.
  - Comic Feature, 1 issue (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Published in Eerie, PA by AMA Fanmag Publications and edited by Larry Walczak.
  - Comic Media, 1972; 1 issue (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Published in London, England and edited by Nick Landau and Dennis Lee.
  - Comic News, 1 issue (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Comic Nostalgia Express, 1984; 1 issue (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Published in Buffalo, NY and edited by Ted Hanes.
  - Comic Press, 1974; 1 issue (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Published in Rochester, NY, an A Publication production and edited by Russell Condello.
  - Comic Times, 1980; 2 issues (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Published in New York, NY by the Comic Times, Inc. and edited by Dennis Cieri.
  - Comic Vendor, 1966; 1 issue (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Published in Upper Saddle River, NJ and edited by Alan Jadro.
  - Comiclub Magazine, 1 issue (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Published in Chicago, IL by GE Publications and edited by Gabe Eisenstein.
  - Comicology Fan Review, 1976; 3 issues (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Published in Adelphi, MD and edited by Doug Fratz.
  - Comics Feature, 1980-1981; 7 issues (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Published in Clearwater, FL by New Media Publishing, Co. and edited by Dean Mullaney.
  - Comics Forever, 1973; 1 issue (Box 2, Folder 13)
    Published by CF Publications and edited by John G. Coyne.
  - Comics Journal, 1977-1980; 34 issues (Box 2, Folder 14-21)
    Published in Riverdale, MD and edited by Gary G. Groth and J. Michael Catron.
  - Comics Land, 1973; 1 issue (Box 2, Folder 22)
    Published in Genova, Italy and edited by Nino Bernazzli.
  - Comics Newsline, 1973; 1 issue (Box 2, Folder 23)
    Published in Lindenhurst, NY and edited by Frank Verzyl.
  - Comicscope, 1972; 1 issue (Box 2, Folder 24)
    Published in East Point, GA by the International Comic Club and edited by C.B. Hackworth.
  - Comix and Fandom, 2 issues (Box 2, Folder 25)
    Published in Pittsburgh, PA and edited by Howard Bender.
  - Comix Unlimited, 1968; 1 issue (Box 2, Folder 26)
    Edited by J. Andriano.
  - Comix Unlimited, 1 issue (Box 2, Folder 27)
    Published in Cranford, NJ and edited by Vincent W. Kimszal.
  - Comix Scene, 1972; 6 issues (Box 2, Folder 28)
    Published in Reading, PA and edited by Steranko and Gary Brown.
  - Compass, 1975; 1 issue (Box 2, Folder 29)
    Published by NCB: National Central Bureau.
  - Complete Justice League of America Reader, 1973; 1 issue (Box 2, Folder 30)
    Edited by Mark Gruenwald and David Lotvers.
  - Connection, 1 issue (Box 2, Folder 31)
    Published in Brooklyn, NY and edited by Americo Figliolini.
  - Cooper's Hero Hobby, 1966-1969; 10 issues (Box 2, Folder 32-33)
    Published in Clarksburg, WV and edited by John R. Cooper.
  - CPL: Contemporary Pictorial Literature, 1973-1975; 7 issues (Box 2, Folder 34)
    Published in Indianapolis, IN and edited by Robert B. Layton and Roger Slifer.
  - Crypt of Comics, 1977; 1 issue (Box 2, Folder 35)
    Published in Seminole, OK and edited by Michael Lail.
  - Dallascon Bulletin, 1969-1971; 4 issues (Box 2, Folder 36)
    Published in Richardson, TX by the Dallascon Bidding Committee and edited by Tom Reamy and Rosemary Hickey.
  - Dangling Conversation, 3 issues (Box 2, Folder 37)
    Published in Wexford, PA by Esser's Coddington's DC Trade Center and edited by David J. Esser.
  - Danske Tegneserier, 1 issue (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Not in English.
  - Dateline: Comicdom, 1976; 1 issue (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Published in Columbus, OH by Crescent Press Publications and edited by Mike Raub.
  - DC Coming Attractions, 1976-1981; 40 issues (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Published in New York City, NY by DC Comics, Inc. and edited by Mike Gold.
  - Deadspawn, 1975-1982; 4 issues (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Published in Norfolk, VA by Apandamandis Productions and edited by Joe Treacy.
  - DFCFR, 1975; 3 issues (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Published in Kenner, LA by D.F. Comicollectors and edited by Don Fortier.
  - Direct Currents, 1978-1979; 13 issues (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Published in New York, NY by DC Comics, Inc. and edited by Joe Orlando and Cary Burkett.
  - Duende, 1977; 1 issue (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - DUFF: Down Under Fan Fund, 1975; 1 issue (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Published in Victoria, Australia and Madison, WI and edited by Leigh Edmonds and Lesleigh Luttrell.
  - Dynamic Magazine, 1970; 1 issue (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Published in East Moline, IL by Dynamic Publications and edited by Alan L. Light.
  - Epitaph, 1975; 1 issue (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Published in Springfield, OH by the Crystal Press and edited by Tom Cameron and Larry Nibert.
  - The Equalizer, 1980; 1 issue (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Edited by Kirk Kennedy.
  - ERB-dom, 1961-1976; 70 issues (Box 3, Folder 12-18)
    Published in Baton Rouge, LA and edited by Camille Cazedessus, Jr.
  - Eric Fromm's Comics and Stories, 1973; 1 issue (Box 3, Folder 19)
    Published in San Francisco, CA by the San Francisco Comic Book Company and edited by Sharon Healy and Gary Arlington.
  - Etcetra, 1971-1973; 6 issues (Box 3, Folder 20)
    Published in Brooklyn, NY by TCR Publications and edited by Paul Levitz and Paul Kupperberg.
  - Etcetera and the Comic Reader, 1971-1972; 10 issues (Box 3, Folder 21)
    Published in Brooklyn, NY and edited by Paul Levitz.
  - Fan Informer, 1974; 2 issues (Box 3, Folder 22)
    Published in Detroit, MI by FFCG: Fantasy Fan Comicollectors Group and edited by Joseph P. Wesson and Arvell M. Jones.
  - Fan To Fan, 1965; 1 issue (Box 3, Folder 23)
    Published in South Bend, IN and edited by Robert E. Butts.
  - The Fandom Annual, 1967; 2 issues (Box 3, Folder 24)
    Published in Miami, Fl by SFCA and edited by G.B. Love.
  - Fandom Funnies, 1976; 1 issue (Box 3, Folder 25)
    Published in Oberlin, OH by Weirdo Publishing Company and edited by Jay L. Zilber.
  - Fandom Marketplace, 1 issue (Box 3, Folder 26)
    Published in Miami, FL by SFCA and edited by Ken Mitchell.
  - Fandom Observer, 1975; 1 issue (Box 3, Folder 27)
    Published in Brooklyn, NY and edited by John Americo Figliolini.
  - The Fandom Spectacular, 1972; 1 issue (Box 3, Folder 28)
    Published in East Moline, IL.
  - Fandom Unlimited, 1971; 1 issue (Box 3, Folder 29)
    Published in Los Altos, CA and edited by Randall D. Larson.
  - Fans of Central Jersey Newsletter, 1976-1977; 5 issues (Box 3, Folder 30)
    Published in North Brunswick, NJ and edited by Bob Andelman.
  - Fan's Zine, 1977; 6 issues (Box 3, Folder 31)
    Published in Columbus, OH by HU Productions and edited by Wally Stoelting.
  - Fan's Zine, 1978; 1 issue (Box 3, Folder 32)
    Published in Loveland, CO by J and J Enterprises and edited by Jan Van Bockel.
  - Fantastic Fanzine, 1970; 2 issues (Box 3, Folder 33)
    Published in Springfield, VA and edited by Gary Groth.
  - Fantastic Fanzine Special, 1972; 1 issue (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - The Fantastic Funnies, 2 issues (Box 3, Folder 35)
    Published in Ontario, Canada by Globe Comics Group.
  - Fantasy Advertiser International, 1978; 1 issue (Box 3, Folder 36)
    Published in Essex, England by Biytoo Books and edited by Colin Campbell.
  - Fantasy Forum, 1 issue (Box 3, Folder 37)
    Published in Pittsburgh, PA by Diamond Publications and edited by Bill Schelly and Rick James.
  - Fantasy Illustrated, 1966; 1 issue (Box 3, Folder 38)
    Published in Los Angeles, CA and edited by Bill Spicer.
  - Fanzine Fanatique, 1958; 14 issues (Box 3, Folder 39)
    Published in Lancaster, England and edited by Keith A. Walker and Daisy Bank.
  - Farther Out, 1975-1980; 12 issues (Box 3, Folder 40)
    Published in Ashtabula, OH and edited by Frank Rizzo.
  - Fem Fantastique, 1 issue (Box 3, Folder 41)
    Edited by Fem Fantastique.
  - First Flight, 1975-1976; 2 issues (Box 3, Folder 42)
    Published in Ashtabula, OH and edited by L.B. Kellogg
  - Flash Comic Special, 1967; 1 issue (Box 3, Folder 43)
    Published in Penn Hills, PA and edited by Raymond Miller.
  - Flying Dutchman, 1981; 1 issue (Box 3, Folder 44)
    Published in Oneonta, NY and edited by Tom Hegeman.
  - Foom Magazine, 1973-1978; 16 issues (Box 4, Folder 1-2)
    Published in New York, NY by Marvel Comics Group and edited by Stan Lee and Steranko.
  - Foreign Comic Reviews, 1973; 1 issue (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Published in Denmark and edited by Carten Sondergaard and Det Lillie Forlag.
  - Frazetta, 1969; 1 issue (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Published by Attezart in Kansas City, MO.
  - Free Fall, 1971-1973; 3 issues (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Published in Huntsville, AL by Sparta Enterprises Diversified and edited by Mike Main.
  - Funnyworld, 1974-1979; 2 issues (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Published in Atlanta, GA and edited by J. Michael Barrier.
  - Futura, 1965; 1 issue (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Published in Jacksonville, FL and edited by Danny Cassidy.
  - Gasp, 1980; 1 issue (Box 4, Folder 8)
    Published in New Bern, NC by Darkstorm Productions and edited by R. Kent Williams and C. Brad Gorby.
  - The Golden Age, 1966; 1 issue (Box 4, Folder 9)
    Published in Miami, FL by the SFCA and edited by G.B. Love.
  - Golden Age Greats, 1974; 1 issue (Box 4, Folder 10)
    Published in Tallahassee, FL by Paragon Publications and edited by William Black.
  - Graphic Art Collectors' International Bulletin, 1967; 2 issues (Box 4, Folder 11)
    Published in Penn Hills, PA and edited by Marshall Lanz.
  - Graphic Fantasy, 1971-1972; 3 issues (Box 4, Folder 12)
    Published in Ogden, UT and edited by Dale R. Broadhurst.
  - Graphic Illusions, 1971; 1 issue (Box 4, Folder 13)
    Published in Van Nuys, CA and edited by Rob and Jeff Gluckson and Rob Gustaveson's.
  - Graphic Showcase, 1967-1970; 3 issues (Box 4, Folder 14)
    Published in Richmond, VA by CCAS Publications and edited by T. Long.
  - Graphic Story Magazine, 1971-1973; 2 issues (Box 4, Folder 15)
    Published in Los Angeles, CA and edited by Bill Spicer AKA William W. Spicer.
  - Graphic Story World, 1971-1972; 7 issues (Box 4, Folder 16)
    Published in Long Beach, CA and edited by Richard Kyle.
  - The Gridley Wave, 1964-1976; 19 issues (Box 4, Folder 17)
    Published in Kansas City, MO by House of Greystoke and edited by Reed Crandall.
  - Hartford Fandom News, 1974; 1 issue (Box 4, Folder 18)
    Published in Glastonbury, CT and edited by John A. Mozzer.
  - Heroes' Hangout, 1963; 1 issue (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - The Heroine Addict, 1974-1977; 10 issues (Box 4, Folder 20)
    Published in Baltimore, MD and later in San Jose, CA by The Comic Heroines Fan Club, a division of the Adventure Heroines Publishing Association. Edited by Albert Tanner and Steven R. Johnson.
  - The Heroine Addict's Art Portfolio, 1976; 1 issue (Box 4, Folder 21)
    Published in Baltimore, MD by the Adventure Heroines Publishing Association and edited by Albert Tanner.
  - The Heroines Showcase, 1977-1979; 3 issues (Box 4, Folder 22)
    Published in Campbell, CA by the Comics Heroines Fan Club and edited by Steven R. Johnson.
  - Hoy!, 1986; 1 issue (Box 4, Folder 23)
    Published in Quezon City, Philippines and edited by Wahoo Guerrero.
  - Id, Ego... Aeon, 1972; 4 issues (Box 4, Folder 24)
    Published in Ontario, Canada and edited by Art Cooper.
  - Imperious Rex, 1 issue (Box 4, Folder 25)
    Published in Jamesburg, NJ and edited by Charlie Hawse.
  - In-Betweena, 1979; 1 issue (Box 4, Folder 26)
    Published in New Brunswick, NJ and edited by Bill-Dale Marcinko.
  - Incognito, 1 issue (Box 4, Folder 27)
    Published in Pittsburgh, PA and edited by Bill Schelly and Rick James.
  - Inside Comics, 1974-1975; 4 issues (Box 4, Folder 28)
    Published in New York, NY and edited by Joe Brancetelli.
  - The Invincible Fanzine, 1976; 2 issues (Box 4, Folder 29)
    Published in Pittsburgh, PA and edited by David Friedlander.
  - JCJ: Jinnia Clan Journal, 1977-1978; 3 issues (Box 4, Folder 30)
    Published in Salem, VA and edited by Jessie Davis, Fred R. Eichelman, and J.L. (Lana) Miersen.
  - The Legion Magazine, 1973; 1 issue (Box 4, Folder 31)
    Published in Pine Plains, NY and edited by Richard Roder.
  - The Legion Outpost, 1973-1974; 2 issues (Box 4, Folder 32)
    Published in Evanston, IL and edited by Harry C. Broertjes.
  - Manticore, 1976; 1 issue (Box 4, Folder 33)
    Published in Dover, NJ and edited by K.M.R. Feduniewicz.
  - The Marvel Art Review, 1976; 2 issues (Box 4, Folder 34)
    Published in Bridgeport, CT and edited by Thom Fagan.
  - Marvel Times, 3 issues (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Marvelmania Monthly Magazine (Check), 1970; 5 issues (Box 4, Folder 36)
    Published in Culver City, CA and edited by Mark Evanier, Bruce Schweiger, Jonathan Yost, and Gary Lowenthal.
  - Media-5, 1976; 1 issue (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Mediascene, 1973-1978; 24 issues (Box 4, Folder 38-42)
    Published in Reading, PA and edited by Steranko.
  - Meet The Dealers, 1977-1978; 4 issues (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Published in New York, NY and edited by Frank C. Verzyl.
  - Melotoons, 1972; 1 issue (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Published in Cleveland, OH and edited by Peter Kuper.
  - Mindrot, 1976; 1 issue (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Published in Minneapolis, MN and edited by David R. Mruz.
  - Mirkwood Times, 1973; 5 issues (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Published in Denver, CO by the Desolation Row Comix Company and edited by Steven J. Allen.
  - Mobile Panelology Association, 1 issue (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Edited by Stephen Barrington.
  - Monitor, 1973; 1 issue (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Edited by Paul Stadinger.
  - Morpheus, 1974-1975; 2 issues (Box 5, Folder 7)
    Published in Minneapolis, MN by the Minnesota Comics and Fantasy Association (MCFA) and edited by David Mruz and Rick Larson.
  - Nebulous, 1971; 2 issues (Box 5, Folder 8)
    Published in Oxon Hill, MD and edited by James Stewart.
  - New York Review of Comics and Books, 1974; 4 issues (Box 5, Folder 9)
    Published in Orange, NJ and edited by Stephen L. Stern.
  - Newton Portfolio Iron Jaw, 1 issue (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Nimbus, 1995-1997; 2 issues (Box 5, Folder 11)
    Published in Morgantown, WV and edited by Frank Lovece.
  - The Nostalgia Journal, 1975-1976; 8 issues (Box 5, Folder 12)
    Published in Lewisville, TX and edited by Joe Bob Williams and Gary G. Groth.
  - Nostalgia News, 1972; 2 issues (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Published in Dallas, TX and edited by Joe Bob Williams.
  - 'Nuff Said?, 1972; 1 issue (Box 5, Folder 14)
    Published in Portland, OR and edited by David Chamberlain.
  - Omniverse, 1977-1979; 2 issues (Box 5, Folder 15)
    Published in New York, NY and edited by Mark Gruenwald.
  - On The Drawing Board, 1966; 1 issue (Box 5, Folder 16)
    Published in St. Louis, MO and edited by Robert Schoenfeld.
  - Oparian, 1965; 1 issue (Box 5, Folder 17)
    Published in Saratoga, CA and edited by Kenneth C. Free.
  - Ophemera, 1977; 1 issue (Box 5, Folder 18)
    Published in Cambridge, MA and edited by Robert M. Stewart.
  - The Panel, 1976-1980; 19 issues (Box 5, Folder 19)
    Published in Ithaca, NY and edited by Tim Gray.
  - Panels, 1979; 1 issue (Box 5, Folder 20)
    Published in New York, NY and edited by John Benson.
  - Panorama, 1971; 1 issue (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Paragon Illustrated, 1969-1972; 2 issues (Box 5, Folder 22)